{
    "1": {
        "question": "Which component of the AWS Global Infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery? (Select the best answer)",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS Regions",
            "B": "AWS Edge locations",
            "C": "AWS Availability Zone",
            "D": "Amazon virtual private cloud (Amazon VPC)"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "You can run applications and workloads from a region closer to the end users to _______ latency.",
        "options": {
            "A": "Increase",
            "B": "Decrease"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "True / False? Networking, storage, compute and databases are examples of service categories that AWS offers.",
        "answer": "T"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "Which of these statements about Availability Zones is not true? (Select the best answer)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Availability Zones are designed for fault isolation",
            "B": "Availability Zones are made up of one or more data centers",
            "C": "Availability zones are connected to each other using high-speed private links",
            "D": "A data center can be used for more than one availability zone"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "What is true about Regions (Choose two)",
        "options": {
            "A": "They are the physical locations of your customers",
            "B": "All regions are located in one specific geographic area",
            "C": "A region is a physical location that has multiple availability zones",
            "D": "Physical location has multiple availability zones",
            "E": "Each region is located in a separate geographic area"
        },
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "answer": [
            "C",
            "E"
        ]
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones? (Select the best answer)",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS Origin",
            "B": "AWS Regions",
            "C": "Compute Zones",
            "D": "Edge Locations"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "_______ means the infrastructure has built-in component redundancy and _______ means that resources dynamically adjust to increases or decreases in capacity requirements.",
        "options": {
            "A": "No human intervention, fault-tolerant",
            "B": "Fault-tolerant, no human intervention",
            "C": "Elastic and scalable, fault-tolerant",
            "D": "Elastic and scalable, no human intervention",
            "E": "E. Fault-tolerant, elastic and scalable"
        },
        "answer": "E"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "True or False? Availability Zones within a region are connected through low-latency links.",
        "answer": "T"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "AWS highly recommends provisioning your compute resources across ____ availability zones.",
        "options": {
            "A": "All",
            "B": "No",
            "C": "Multiple",
            "D": "Single"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "True or False? Edge locations are only located in the same general area as regions.",
        "answer": "F"
    }
}